ORIGINAL WORK BY TATSUYA ENDO
SERIALIZED ON SHUEISHA'S SHONEN JUMP PLUS
MISSION:11 STELLA
No way. Everyone we're pursuing is…
Let's go back to the hideout and regroup.
I have a bad feeling about this…
SCIENCE - ANYA FORGER: F
LANGUAGE - ANYA FORGER: F
No way!
Bondman! This can't be happening!
I can't believe I did this!
Hey! Get a grip!
-Hey, Anya.
-Anya's busy right now.
This tragedy is…
No! I don't want to study!
Hey! Wait!
You promised you'd start studying
at five o'clock!
You're evil!
-Operation Strix. Phase two.
-Father, you're evil!
In order to be present at the reception
where the target will appear,
I must make my daughter Anya
an Imperial Scholar.
To do so, she must achieve
excellent grades and earn Stellas…
PROVERB QUESTION
How many times do I need to tell you?
It's E, not A.
But Loid, her math scores aren't too bad!
You did well, Anya!
Remaining bullets are 2/8.
Is that thanks to the anime?
That's right!
This proverb here. Bondman said
the same thing in episode 16!
I don't remember…
Remember!
The episode with
the guy with the sideburns!
I just happened to misread
everyone's minds
for this test.
From now on, I'll take my time
and figure out which classmates are good
at which subjects.
SKILLS:??
Then Anya will for sure
get a perfect score. It'll be fine.
I tried saying that like Father.
I can easily switch
the test results to an A-plus,
but suddenly getting a high score
will arouse suspicion
from the school and others.
In order to make it look natural,
we must improve her basic academic skills.
If her friends start to alienate her,
her school life may suffer.
-I can't have her stop going to school…
-Everyone will hate me?
If I get perfect scores
by reading people's minds?
How do you know that?
What a creepy witch!
I guess forcing her to study
is a bit harsh.
Without motivation, she won't be focused
and her learning efficiency will be poor.
It's important to take a break too.
There are ways to obtain Stellas
aside from studying.
Okay. Let's stop studying and draw!
For example, art.
Wow! How cool!
Is that a cheetah? No, wait.
It must be a panda!
It's a cow… The one from school.
For example, music!
Here's a violin for children!
Then, sports!
Oh…
Oh, don't cry.
Relax, Twilight…
A journey of a thousand miles begins with
a single step. She's only in first grade.
I have to take the time to find out
her strengths and cultivate them.
Shall we do some jump rope? It'll be fun!
That's right. Don't rush it.
It's not like Desmond will
make his move right away.
Planning for war takes
an extensive amount of time.
However…
Headquarters estimates that eight Stellas
should be achieved in about four months.
Do we really have time for that?
Father, Anya will do her best!
Just take this rope off me already.
Okay.
-Anya?
-Hm?
Shall we go out tomorrow?
Excur-gen?
In addition to academics, arts and sports,
there's another way to acquire a Stella.
Social contribution!
Thank you for participating in our
parent-child volunteer program today.
Now, I will explain your duties.
-We'll have you split into families…
-It's happened.
Many have received the award for
their long-term commitment to service.
People have been awarded for saving lives
or assisting in the apprehension
of criminals, but it's rare.
Although it's possible to give support
using the organization's personnel,
it's not easy to do considering
the various risks involved.
Well, even if it doesn't lead to
Stellas right away,
there's no harm in letting Anya develop
a spirit of social contribution.
Well then,
Mr. Forger, could you please start by
cleaning this changing room?
There's a pool!
For the patients' rehabilitation.
Oh…
Maybe cleaning was a little difficult.
Then, can I have you
organize books in the library?
Excuse me, sir. Look…!
Could you go do a different job?
Anya's bored of chores.
I want to be the person
who hands the knife to the doctor.
I'm going to the surgery room!
Wh…! Hey! Wait! Stop!
We've had enough! Please go home!
Father… I'm sorry.
Don't worry. Everyone makes mistakes.
But what if there's no hope
for a Stella even in social contribution?
Hey. Is rehab hard?
It's hard but in order
to be able to run again, you have to try!
Three more minutes!
Is the water in the pool cold?
It'll be fine! Go change!
I'm going to go change too.
Okay! One, two…
I guess that's the adult pool.
Focus on those toes!
-A little more to go!
-It's cold…
Ah…
Ken?
Huh? Maybe he's still changing…
Maybe I should have Headquarters
rethink our plan…
I… can't breathe… My legs… won't move…
The pool!
-Father!
-What? You just went to the bathroom.
Someone is drowning in the pool!
Huh? How do you know that?! What are you?!
Help me…
Father…
Anya sucks at volunteer work…
So…
I'll become a swimmer and get a Stella,
so I'm going to go practice in the pool!
What! Hey! Wait! It's not a public pool!
Ken?
I guess he backed out, huh?
Hey!
Whose kid are you?!
Wow! The pool is so fun!
What is she doing?
Where is the kid who's drowning?
I'm going to die…
What are you doing?!
Anya can't…
Are you guys okay?!
Ken!
Father…
-Someone call a doctor!
-When I tried to swim…
-This kid was dying…
-Ken!
Are you okay?!
-Relax.
Ken!
And there were so many people around…
-Did you hear anything?
-I'm sorry!
I didn't think you were drowning!
It's the instinctive drowning response.
Children are awfully quiet
when they drown.
There are a lot of cases where they die
because people don't notice.
Please don't take your eyes off them.
But, good job noticing.
I saw bubbles, so…
Don't overdo it.
Thank you!
Well done, little girl!
Anya Forger! First year from Cecile Hall!
We award you a Stella for saving a life!
Anya, you're amazing!
You're the first in first grade!
-Ultra-amazing elegant,
-I'm so proud of you too!
-Ms. Forger.
-You did it, Anya!
She beat me to it.
How amazing, Anya! You're really amazing!
I'm so happy!
We achieved a Stella unexpectedly.
It's an amazing result…
but…
more importantly,
I feel as proud as the time when
I prevented a terrorist attack.
You did well!
Anya's power was able to help someone…
Yes.
Okay! I'm going to make
a delicious meal today!
Anya want's Father's cooking.
TO BECOME AN HONOR STUDENT -
7 MORE STELLAS
TO GET EXPELLED - 7 MORE TONITOS
EVERYONE'S RESPECT - 100+
I hear your daughter
received a Stella, Agent Twilight.
Yes, Handler. Thank goodness.
At this rate, we can't keep
using other agents
to take credit for our work…
It would look suspicious.
Above all, you can't risk exposing
the identities of your
valuable personnel
or getting them arrested.
I guess…
Is Headquarters getting impatient?
No, but suspicious
money activity has increased
at several businesses around Desmond.
The situation doesn't look promising.
Get in close contact with Desmond
as soon as possible.
Give your daughter some candy
to motivate her.
-Good morning!
-Did you see yesterday's…
I forgot my homework!
Wow isn't that the girl? The girl from
Class 3 who suddenly got a Stella?
-They say it's the fastest record.
-For saving a life, right?
The star is so bright
that Anya stands out.
Hello, Anya!
-No.
-Huh?
Call me "Starlight Anya."
Huh? Oh… Okay…
You're so popular now!
Everyone respects you!
You'll make 100 friends!
I've underestimated you, Anya!
Be my friend!
Come over to my house!
And invite your parents!
Bam!
Good job, Anya! With this,
the mission is accomplished!
The world is finally at peace.
Don't let this go to your head.
What's with him? He pisses me off!
This isn't what I'd planned for…
The world's in trouble…
Let's go, Anya!
-Let's go, Starlight Anya.
-Okay.
How annoying.
How silly.
She's being so snooty about it!
She's taking this opportunity to
show off her badge!
I mean, who would actually come to school
wearing it?
There's no way a violent girl like her
saved a life.
They say she saved a drowning kid,
but she probably pushed him in
to begin with!
That's so true!
Or maybe they paid a lot of money
to the school and bought the Stella!
What? They don't look that rich.
Darn…
Don't worry about it.
They're just jealous.
You agree with us, right, Damian?
She totally cheated.
You think our school is
a third-rate school
that would give a Stella
accidentally or unjustly?
Oh… no…
If you're unhappy with the school,
take a transfer test and go elsewhere.
He's so manly
when it comes to these things!
How cool!
It pisses me off even more that
that little pest beat me to it,
because I know it wasn't a fluke!
Maybe he's a pretty good guy, after all.
Let's start class!
By the way, have you decided
what your reward will be, Anya--
-Starlight Anya.
-Reward?
That's right! When you do your best
with a test or a contest,
a reward is a must!
-Can I get peanuts?
-Something more expensive than that!
After the last test, my parents bought me
a cute dress and a tiara!
But I guess…
I haven't really received
anything extravagant.
Is your household a secret organization
that is secretly controlling the world?
What are you saying?
It's a legitimate company!
Then Anya wants a castle!
I think that's a bit impossible.
There'll be nowhere to put it.
Then a year's worth of peanuts.
I'm sure that'll be easy, but…
That's all you want?
Rewards are hard…
Well, I guess the gift that made me
most happy was
Wiesel!
Oh, that's my dog! She's so cute!
A dog?
Second son, do you have a dog too?
Huh? A dog?
Why are you asking him?
Max!
Who knows!
Don't talk to me so casually!
Anya's house has a dog now too!
Awesome! Let's compete over
who's dog is cuter! Yours or Max!
Bring him over to my house!
And your parents too!
Hello, Mr. Forger.
Let's stop this war, Mr. Desmond.
The world is finally at peace.
You want a dog as a reward?
It'll be peaceful if we get a dog.
Peaceful? Your mind?
Hm… Well, I was thinking about
getting you something…
Anya,
taking care of an animal is a tough job.
It comes with responsibility.
Responsibility?
A dog, huh? Okay.
Let's think about it.
-Loid!
-Father!
If it's a properly trained dog,
it might be good for
the security of this house.
Dogs can be violent…
I'm worried that Anya
may be bitten to bits!
Anya wants a cute doggy. A small one.
Huh? Oh, okay.
I'm sure there are small but capable dogs.
Maybe I'll have the organization
prepare one for me.
Okay, let's go to the pet shop
this weekend.
Have you decided where to sell?
I'm still figuring it out.
They're all a bunch of
revolutionary-minded punks.
Are they thinking of making them
bomb dogs?
How pathetic.
They're just manipulated to become
toys for humans.
Shut up! If you want food, keep it down!
They don't look like smart dogs to me.
Don't number three
and number five look tame?
Who cares! Just leave them.
-This place stinks!
-Let's go home already.
Anya wants this one or this one!
I'm glad, they look tame!
MISSION:12 PENGUIN PARK
Subtitle translation by: Nana Onishi